For most of the Indian travellers,
getting a good travel insurance is absolutely
useless as their money gets stuck.  That's what
they think.  But you must have a good
travel insurance
because it is about your life.  You are
going to another country, it can be Europe, it
can be US, Canada, Australia.
If you get sick there then you need to pay a
lot.  So
travel insurance is the best option to save those things.  Along
with that, your flight gets delayed or cancelled.
Your bag gets lost or your
passport gets lost.  So in that you
get compensation as per your policy.
How is the price of travel insurance
determined?  That depends on your
country.  The premiums in the US and Canada are generally
slightly higher.  Compared to Sensual, Asian
and other countries.  A lot of
people ask about student travel insurance.
So you
can also purchase travel insurance from all these companies.
Which will be valid.  Which companies
are approved outside India?  To
sell travel insurance.  There are many foreign
companies.  You will get the list.
These are all the companies of secondary India.
I have taken the details from the official website of VFS Global.
You can purchase the plan of any of these companies.  They are
fully valid.  Before choosing a good travel insurance,
you have to cross-check
different plans and their PD
period.  Secondary local currency was found.
Let's say you are travelling to US.  The payment should
get you coverage in USD.
That is good.  Same Goes to Australia and
Any Other Country.  The sanctioned reason is also that the amount should be
in Euro.  What
is included in the coverage?  Is secondary dental cover included
or not?  Because sometimes problems occur.
We are going to travel and there is a
toothache or some problem.  So that's it.
You definitely get accidental cover.  You have to
see the amount that you need.  A good
travel insurance will only cost you 1%.
But in exchange, you will get assistance in all the problems like medical bills, flight
delay and cancellation, baggage loss, passport
loss etc.
247 I would
suggest you to compare the policies on the market once.
That will give you an idea.
And here in the destination let's say
Goa may be 16 to 20 and in five
days trip may be one person age is 28 no and
this is why no it was a five day trip so
all these plans came in front of us and all these
plans are valid for ₹500 this is available for ₹800
you can compare any of these you can purchase any of them
and the best thing about policy
bazaar could be you can call the representative
and ask all the questions and you should
ask and after that they
help you a lot in claim settlement also.
So you can definitely consider I
trust policy, I have been using it for the last 4 years.